And today, we are going to be doing a method or a technique called a stepping stone.
And what we're going to do is we're going to be using art glass and/or stained glass for the surface of the stone, and then it's going to be poured with a bunch of grout.
Believe it or not, these things are incredibly durable.
In fact, not only durable, they're heavy.
So anyway, they are for your flower beds, your walkways, your--people even keep them in the house.
They're so pretty. They are strong enough to step on. They're strong enough for water. They're going to make it through the seasons, if you do the couple of techniques to make it help--last through the ages.
They are strong enough to step on, like I said, but people think they're too pretty to step on.
So don't worry about it.
I'm going to show you what to do and have fun with it.
So what we're going to do, we actually need a mold.
These are called stepping-stone molds.
They come in a variety of sizes and, of course, they're available at your local stained glass store.
So anyway, they are fairly expensive, I think, but as far as many stones that you can get them, they're actually worth every penny.
In fact, they turn out to be quite cheap at that point.
So anyway, find a size you like or start with a pattern first.
So check it out on the next step.